[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
I...
I like Serizawa.
From now on, I'll match your speed.
My speed?
So, that's what this is all about.
He said he has a crush on someone.
He's been crushing on them since his first year.
Woah, he's so loyal.
I wonder who Serizawa's crush is.
Let me see your hand.
Of course a guy like him would have a dazzling romance.
Sorry!
Matsuno?
Suzuki...
Sorry about that. Here, use this.
Thanks.
You don't need to give that back to me.
Suzuki.
Never mind.
Suzuki?
Is everything okay?
Yeah, thanks.
Was he trying to make up with you?
No. Things are still pretty awkward between us.
We used to be best friends
back in freshman year though.
But I'm your bestest friend now, right?
That's something I won't budge on.
Personal space!
If anything, I wanted to be friends back in freshman year, too.
I also wish we'd known each other earlier.
Right, I almost forgot to ask.
Wanna go to the beach with me?
- The beach? - Yeah.
Let's go and make summer memories together.
The beach...
[Episode 8]
Summer memories...
Suzuki!
Over here!
Together, with just Serizawa.
I guess not, huh?
Is that Suzupi?
Hey, what's up!
You came to join us!
Awesome!
Come on, let's go!
Yeah.
Three, two, one...
Looking good!
Hold on.
No one told me the girls were joining, too.
Extroverted popular kids are built different.
Maybe one of them is Serizawa's crush.
Is it Miyamoto?
Takahashi?
Sakuraba?
No, she's Saeki's girlfriend.
Suzuki.
Why are you staring at the girls?
No, I...
Come join the rest of us.
You aren't gonna take a dip?
Well...
You know.
Everyone else looks so dazzling, so...
Hey, don't exclude yourself.
We're making summer memories together, right?
- Yeah. - Come on.
Huh?
You're out.
- Serizawa! - That's your fault for just standing there.
You asked for it!
I hate to admit it.
But whenever I'm with Serizawa,
he always ropes me into his schemes.
I can't deny it.
I...
Around you go!
Serizawa! Pause!
Stop it!
Stop spinning me!
- Reon. - Yeah?
- Let me have a sip. - Huh?
That's not a sip.
- Cheapskate. - Give it back.
More! More!
There!
Cover his legs.
What's up?
Does Serizawa have a crush on...
Here.
Huh? You sure?
Actually, 10,000 yen for the bottle.
That's too expensive.
- Thanks. - Anytime.
You having fun?
Yeah.
I just wonder if the others actually want me here.
Of course they do.
You might not realize it, but we all enjoy your company.
Thanks.
You're a nice guy, Takeuchi.
Nah, I wouldn't say that.
Say, can I ask something?
Have you all been friends since freshman year?
Yeah.
I was in a different class though.
I see.
Then...
You two are drinking ramune?
No fair!
Where's our share?
Get your own bottles.
- The vendor's over there. - Rude!
Serizawa, could you get us some?
Why me?
We're all thirsty, me included.
Please?
Fine.
Suzuki, you're coming with.
Suzuki?
- Come on. - Huh?
- Serizawa? - Yeah?
You're still holding my hand.
I know.
Are you mad?
No.
Why were you staring so hard at Reon?
Because you two seemed like good friends.
So what?
Wait, were you jealous of her?
No. That's not it.
To tell you the truth,
I overheard our upperclassmen talking, and...
They said you had a crush on someone.
Huh?
I thought maybe it was Miyamoto.
No, it's not.
Then is it Takahashi?
No.
Sakuraba?
Saeki's girlfriend? Of course not.
Right, I thought so.
But I do have a crush.
You haven't noticed?
We're always together, my crush and I.
Really?
They're a nice person.
Very cute, kind,
and hardworking, too.
Unfortunately, they're also very dense.
We were finally placed in the same class this year,
and I've been making moves, but they still haven't noticed.
That's another reason why they're so cute.
And I love them all the more for it.
So?
Can you guess who I'm talking about?
More?
You're definitely lying.
It needs fuel!
How about that?
Give me the tongs.
You're not doing it right.
What?
I had no idea who he was talking about.
Honestly, I was too nervous to really process what he was saying.
How hasn't he caught on by now?
He's the king of being dense.
I gave him plenty of hints to work with!
This is Suzuki we're talking about.
Hints won't do the trick.
Just say it outright already.
Follow my lead.
- "Suzuki! I..." - Shh!
You think it's so easy.
I've been inching closer to him since freshman year,
only to finally become friends with him.
I won't let Suzuki get away.
Terrifying.
Still, I get how you feel.
Confessing could put the other in an awkward spot.
Exactly.
If only I knew that Suzuki
felt anything for me.
I do wonder what he thinks of me.
No way. Really?
Who is it?
Who is Serizawa's crush?
Suzuki.
Thanks for joining us.
No problem.
I like cooking, anyway.
I meant at the beach today.
- Huh? - By the way,
how'd you become friends with Serizawa?
I know we asked before, but we never got an answer.
Was there something that brought you two together?
Actually...
it was because I like BL.
BL?
Yeah.
Right. I forgot Serizawa's a BL fan.
You knew?
Yeah. He read it often during freshman year.
I've read a bit, too. It's interesting!
Yeah.
He started reading it totally out of the blue.
Huh?
Yeah, I remember.
He said he picked it up
because of his crush.
His crush...
Hold on.
Doesn't that mean...
Seriously?
That's why?
I don't understand.
Tastes like protein.
Here, try a bite.
- Away you go. - Woah!
- Now that the pest is gone. - Yeah.
Here.
Ready?
Go for it.
Smells good.
In other words, Serizawa's crush...
He's been crushing on them since his first year.
is someone he met in freshman year.
But they only became classmates this year.
You haven't noticed?
We're always together, my crush and I.
His crush is also always with him,
and is a fellow BL fan?
Who could it be? No one fits the bill...
Suzuki, are you eating?
Here.
Hold it right there!
- What? - Here.
Take the one I grilled.
Who cares who grilled it? It's all the same.
Is not.
Meat is always grilled with love.
- Love? - Love.
- Okay... - Here.
Thanks.
You're not making any sense.
Wait a second...
I want to read your work.
I'm a fellow BL lover, after all.
You too?
I've been reading the stuff since before Serizawa.
I was in a different class though.
Is his crush...
Suzuki?
Are you not hungry?
No, I am.
Takeuchi, you and Serizawa went to the same middle school, right?
Yeah.
Were you two ever in the same class?
No. This year's the first time we're together.
But we really only became friends
in freshman year of high school.
We were both on the library committee.
Why?
No reason.
Crap, my marshmallow's burning.
Takeuchi, help! Hurry!
Why in the world is it burning?
Yikes! Help!
Get it out of there!
Fan it.
There is one person
who completely fits the bill.
Woah!
There it goes!
Cute!
I'm living my youth!
I get it. Anyone would like Takeuchi.
He's kind, confident,
and just a good guy overall.
Still...
Serizawa, let me light mine.
Serizawa.
What am I supposed to do?
My chest hurts so much.
Those two are different!
- Are they? - Yeah!
Excuse me.
Hup.
What's up, Suzuki?
Let's enjoy the fireworks together.
Right.
Here, take one.
- A sparkler? - Yeah.
It'll make for a great summer memory, don't you think?
Did you know?
If your sparkler lasts the entire stick,
your wish will come true.
A wish?
Yeah.
I'll tell you mine.
I wish my crush will like me forever.
Hold it right there!
Meat is always grilled with love.
- Love? - Love.
So close.
Your turn.
Here.
You aren't going to make a wish?
No.
I'll pass.
We're going out as a class after this. Wanna join?
No matter how many times you lost heart,
you still continued to write.
That's seriously amazing, you know?
Next time, at least say a quick bye, okay?
I'm a huge fan of BL, too.
What's so wrong about that?
See?
I told you they wouldn't judge.
Thanks, Serizawa.
Accept the fact
that I think you're awesome.
You're adorable, Suzuki.
You're at the top of my list of people I want at my side.
I like Serizawa after all.
What about you, Suzuki?
Do you have a crush on anyone?
That's why...
No, I don't.
I see.
I'll choose to root for Serizawa.
I've been so lonely.
I wanted to do this.
If we stay together,
I'm sure...
What do I do?